SRILANKAN AIRLINES - BAGGAGE AND UNACCOMPANIED BAGGAGE RULES

1. Unaccompanied Baggage is shipped as cargo and is charged per kilogram.
2. It must only contain personal effects, clothing, and books.
3. Restricted items in Unaccompanied Baggage: No perfumes, no aerosols, no electronics with lithium batteries, and no valuables.
4. Maximum weight per single piece of unaccompanied baggage is 32kg for safety and handling reasons.
